earnearnearn.org 2012-06-28

# Privacy Policy & Terms - The site where you Earn Earn Earn - Earn Earn Earn

**Privacy Policy and Terms for www.earnearnearn.org**

If you require any further information or have any questions no matter what they are about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at steve6999@hotmail.co.uk.

At www.isascam.co.uk the privacy of our visitors is of the most extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.isascam.co.uk and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.isascam.co.uk makes some use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, types of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date & time stamp, referring and exit pages, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.isascam.co.uk does not use cookies at all.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, as with most sites uses cookies to serve ads on www.isascam.co.uk.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.isascam.co.uk and other sites on the Internet this is normal on most sites.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.isascam.co.uk send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.isascam.co.uk has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.isascam.co.uk’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### **No Refunds Are Issued.**

Categories: [Earn Earn Earn](http://earnearnearn.org/earnearnearn/ "View all posts in Earn Earn Earn")  Tags:
